Benjamin Wakefield

Personal details

Address: 6 Langdon Lane

Bellmere 4510

Mobile: 0499 794 102

Email: <u>bwakefield34@gmail.com</u>

Career Goal

I am currently studying at the Fast Track Coding Bootcamp at Coder Academy and will afterwards be able to call myself a Full Stack Developer! Once I've completed the course I hope to find employment in the tech industry, in software or games development preferably. I've been coding as a pastime in C# on a Unity project for the last two years, but since starting the course in August I've now learnt how to use Terminal, HTML and CSS, and having built my own website.

Personal Skills

- Strong problem solving skills
- Polite and courteous
- Curious and inquisitive; not afraid to ask questions
- High attention to detail; Analytical
- Quick Learner

Employment History

Burrell Stockbroking & Superannuation (Spring Hill)

2017 – Present

- Office Clerk
- Filing physical copies of distribution, dividend and account statements by account holder
- Opening and sorting mail
- Correcting errors on statements in databases

Vuly Trampolines (Wynnum)

2014 - 2014

- Customer Service
- Over-the-phone Customer Support
- Customer Complaints Handling
- Online Customer Support

K Mart (Morayfield)
Lay-by Counter

2011 - 2012

Education History

Coder Academy (Fast-Track)

2020 - Present

- Terminal, Bash
- HTML
- CSS, SCSS

Bachelor of Business (QUT Gardens Point) Majoring in Finance

2015 - 2018

Extracurricular History

Nudge-athon (QUT Gardens Point)

2017

- Competition between behavioural economics students from universities across Australia
- In a team, developed a solution to the underrepresentation of volunteering among young people in three days and presented it to judges from the University of Warwick, as well as representatives from the Australian Government.
- Unique experience gained in time critical, team oriented problem solving
- Increase ability to critically analyse competing ideas and make decisions within strict time constraints
- Learned to efficiently allocate tasks by knowledge, time, and effort available from each team member

Work-Experience

Work experience Bunnings (Northlakes) Replenishment 2014

Work experience Micro Ed (Morayfield) 2010

Computer technician assistant

References

Elaine Anderson

- Burrell Stockbroking and Superannuation: Director - Portfolio Services

Phone: (07) 3006 7236

Email: eanderson@burrell.com.au

Davinder Saini

- Vuly Trampolines Wynnum: Accounts Manager

Mobile: 0432 842 536

Email: davinder.s@vulyplay.com

Russell Meyers

- Origin Energy: Senior Project Engineer

Mobile: 0406412719